{
    "subject": "resource/Princesse_Tam-Tam",
    "predicate": "property/cinematography",
    "object": "Georges Beno\u00eet",
    "human_readable": "The cinematography of Princesse Tam-Tam was done by Georges Beno\u00eet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.962367594242096,
            "question": "Who is the cinematographer of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9605622291564941,
            "question": "Who did the cinematography for Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9321181774139404,
            "question": "What type of work did Georges Beno\u00eet do on Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911163330078125,
            "question": "What role did Georges Beno\u00eet play in the making of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8961672782897949,
            "question": "Georges Beno\u00eet worked as a ______ for Princesse Tam-Tam."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8955580592155457,
            "question": "Is Georges Beno\u00eet known for cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8775560259819031,
            "question": "What was Georges Beno\u00eet's contribution to Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7460599541664124,
            "question": "Name a film by Georges Beno\u00eet."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6970926523208618,
            "question": "What film is Georges Beno\u00eet known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.654643714427948,
            "question": "Georges Beno\u00eet worked on which movie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematography of Princesse Tam-Tam was done by Georges Beno\u00eet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1289_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is Georges Beno\u00eet known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1289_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film by Georges Beno\u00eet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1289_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Georges Beno\u00eet's contribution to Princesse Tam-Tam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1289_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1289_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason is that there is no information in any of the documents about the cinematography of Princesse Tam-Tam being done by Georges Beno\u00eet. However, one document does mention a \"cinematographer\" without specifying the name."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents explicitly states that \"cinematographer: Georges Beno\u00eet\" for the film \"Princesse Tam-Tam,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention the cinematographer of Princesse Tam-Tam as Georges Beno\u00eet, instead, it specifically states that \"cinematographer: Georges Beno\u00eet\" after listing a series of facts about the film, but then only mentions Edmond Greville in relation to the director of Princesse Tam-Tam.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}